<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecycleBeeV1</string>
    <string name="no_account">Not registered? Sign up <b>here</b></string>
    <string name="sign_in">Already have an account? <b>Sign in</b></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="new1">Paper that can be recycled: newspapers, magazines, telephone books, office paper, junk mail, comics and light cardboard. </string>
    <string name="new12">Preparation: Ensure items are clean from any organic material like food or grease. </string>
    <string name="new2">Plastic that can be recycled: Plastic bottles, bottle tops and cartons.</string>
    <string name="new22">Preparation: Plastic items placed in your recycling bin need to be clean, dry and loose. This means there should be no food or liquids left on/in your plastic items, and you should place all the items loosely in the bin </string>
    <string name="new3">Tins/Cans that can be recycled: Drink cans, aluminion foil, soup/sauce/fruit tins, food cans, biscuit tins, pet food cans, beer bottle lids. </string>
    <string name="new32">Preparation:Empty and rinse items – left over foods or liquids can contaminate other recyclables. You can leave labels on – these are removed in the recycling process. Metal lids and caps can also be placed in the household recycling bin.</string>
    <string name="new4">Batteries that can be recycled: Household batteries (AA, AAA, C, C, 9-volt) can be brought to battery recycling stations. Stores like Aldi and Lidl have battery recycling stations in store - Look for the blue box at tills! </string>
    <string name="new42">Preparation:</string>
    <string name="new5">Glass that can be recycled: All types of glass: green, clear and brown are fine to recycle</string>
    <string name="new52">Preparation: Clean, dry and loose. Some recycling banks will require separation of clear, green and brown glass. </string>
    <string name="new6">Donate pre-loved garments, shoes and soft furnishings to local charity shops or use the charity textile bins at bring centres and other locations.</string>
    <string name="new62">Preparation: Some textiles are not suitable for re-use or recycling such as those that are heavily soiled or worn, these should be disposed of in a clothes bank where they will be sent for shredding and used, for instance, as furniture stuffing.</string>
</resources>